Who is that girl?
I haven't seen her around.
She's pretty.
Hey, you, the student over there!
You shouldn't be out this late!
Hurry back to the dorm!
You must have heard about the sightings of a pervert on school grounds.
Yes, ma'am!
Wait, are you...
a new transfer student?
Y-Yes!
There are molesters and peeping toms around.
Be careful.
Thank you for your concern.
Why doesn't anyone notice that it's me?!
Fight for the sky
afuredasu kanjou mou tomaranai
I can't stop the overflowing emotions
mune ni idaitai bokura no gensou
The illusions we hold so dear
Just revolution
kienai aza ni obiete ite mo
Fear of the scar that won't disappear
toki ga mujou ni sugiteku dake
Won't stop the ruthless passage of time
susumeyo aru ga mama
Go forth, the way you are
Let's burst up!
ima koso kawaru toki
Now is the time for change
Let's boost up!
kakumei no kane no ne ga
The sound of the bell of revolution
doko made mo hibiite yuku
Resounds far and wide
To be the soldier
mou koko ni wa irarenai
We can't stay here any longer
To be the soldier
kaze wo kitte yuke ikite yuke
Cut through the wind, live your life
hiryuu no gotoku
Like a flying dragon
hajimari ga michiru mama densetsu ni nare
As the beginning draws near, become a legend
tokihanatte yuke tonde yuke
Release yourself, fly ahead
inochi wo tagirasete
Overflow with life
erabareshi mono wo matsu sekai wa owari da New age
The world that waits for a chosen one is over! New age!
m 630.875 727 b 624.5 728.875 619.5 727.75 616.625 720.25 614.875 715.375 612 710.875 609.25 706.5 608.5 705.25 606.5 704.875 605.125 704.25 604.5 705.375 603.25 706.75 603.375 707.875 604.25 714.25 600.125 721.75 609 727 601.875 727 595.875 727 589.625 727 597.25 720 597.375 682.875 589.625 676.75 599.125 676.75 608.25 676.125 617.25 677 622.75 677.375 626.75 681.25 627.625 687.25 628.5 693.375 626.25 698 620.875 701.125 619.625 701.875 618.375 702.375 616.125 703.625 621 711.375 625.875 719 630.875 727 m 603.75 677.75 b 603.75 686.75 603.75 693.25 603.75 702.125 609 699.875 614.625 699.125 617 696 619.125 693.25 619.125 686.5 617.125 683.75 614.75 680.625 609.125 680 603.75 677.75 m 1212.125 714.875 b 1207.5 709.625 1205.125 703.625 1209.75 697.5 1214.5 691.125 1221.375 690.75 1228.75 692.5 1232.875 693.5 1237.25 693.25 1241.75 695 1239.875 695.625 1238 696.25 1236.25 696.875 1240.5 711 1235.125 717.75 1220.5 717.375 1218.125 717.25 1215.75 719 1213.375 720 1215.75 721 1218.125 722.5 1220.75 723 1224.875 723.75 1229.5 722.75 1233.25 724.25 1236.5 725.5 1240.5 728.875 1241 731.875 1241.5 734.875 1239.25 740 1236.5 741.875 1228.125 747.75 1218.5 747.5 1209.375 743.625 1202.75 740.625 1203.625 734.875 1211.25 728.5 1206 722.125 1206 721.875 1212.125 714.875 m 1223.125 728.875 b 1223.125 729 1223.125 729 1223.125 729.125 1221.125 729.125 1218.625 728.375 1217.25 729.375 1215 730.875 1212.75 733.25 1212 735.75 1211.5 737.375 1213.875 741.375 1215.125 741.5 1220.625 741.875 1226.25 741.625 1231.625 740.625 1233 740.25 1234.75 736.5 1234.5 734.5 1234.25 732.625 1231.75 730.625 1229.75 729.625 1227.875 728.75 1225.375 729.125 1223.125 728.875 m 1231.5 706.25 b 1229.5 699.75 1228.75 694.5 1222.375 694.75 1216.625 694.875 1215.5 700 1215.5 704.5 1215.5 709.375 1216.75 715.125 1223 714 1226.25 713.5 1228.75 709 1231.5 706.25 m 971 727.25 b 968.625 727.25 964.125 727.25 959.5 727.25 964.75 718.625 962.375 709.25 961.875 700.25 961.75 698.625 958.25 695.5 957.375 695.75 954.125 697.125 949.125 699.25 948.75 701.625 947.75 709.875 948.375 718.375 948.375 727.125 945.875 727.125 941.25 727.125 936.625 727.125 942 719.625 941.875 683.125 936 677.5 940 676.25 943.625 675.25 947.875 673.875 947.875 681.5 947.875 688.5 947.875 695.375 948.75 695.625 949.375 696 949.5 695.75 954.5 692.375 959.625 689.75 965.5 693 971.375 696.375 970.25 702.375 970.375 707.75 970.625 714.125 970.75 720.625 971 727.25 m 1035.125 714.375 b 1036.25 716.5 1037.125 718.625 1038.375 720.625 1041.125 725 1047.875 726.375 1052.125 723.375 1056.625 720.25 1057.625 713.75 1053.375 709.625 1049.5 705.875 1044.75 703.125 1040.375 699.75 1033 694 1031.25 686.25 1036 680.25 1040.125 675 1054.125 672.25 1058.75 676.75 1061 679 1061 683.5 1062 687 1061.125 687.375 1060.375 687.625 1059.5 688 1058.625 686.375 1058.125 684.25 1056.875 683.125 1054.625 681.125 1051.75 678.625 1049.25 678.625 1046.625 678.625 1042.75 681.125 1041.875 683.375 1041 685.625 1042.375 689.875 1044.25 691.875 1047.875 695.5 1052.5 698.25 1056.875 701.125 1062.875 705.375 1065.125 711.125 1063.25 718.125 1061.5 724.75 1056.125 727.875 1049.75 728.125 1033.875 729 1032.375 726.375 1035.125 714.375 m 804.375 727.125 b 800.75 727.125 796.375 727.125 791.75 727.125 796.75 718 794.75 708.625 793.75 699.375 793.625 698 790.125 695.375 789.25 695.75 786.125 697.125 781.125 699.375 780.875 701.75 779.875 710 780.5 718.5 780.5 727.25 777.875 727.25 773.25 727.25 768.5 727.25 774.125 720 774 701.25 768.5 695.875 778.25 691.625 778.25 691.625 780.625 696.5 782.5 695.375 784.125 694 786 693 794.5 689 801.875 693.25 802.375 702.5 802.625 707.25 802.25 712 802.625 716.625 802.875 720.125 803.75 723.625 804.375 727.125 m 1176.875 727.125 b 1173.75 727.125 1169.25 727.125 1164.375 727.125 1170 720.25 1169.875 701.625 1163.75 694.75 1168.5 695.875 1173.125 688.25 1176.75 696.25 1178.625 695.125 1180.5 693.75 1182.5 692.875 1190.875 689.25 1197.75 693.25 1198.25 702.375 1198.625 707.375 1198.125 712.375 1198.5 717.375 1198.625 720.5 1199.625 723.75 1200.25 727.125 1196.625 727.125 1192.25 727.125 1189.75 727.125 1189.875 718 1190.125 708.875 1189.75 699.875 1189.75 698.375 1186.5 695.5 1185.625 695.75 1182.5 696.75 1177.5 698.625 1177.25 700.625 1176.375 709.125 1176.875 717.75 1176.875 727.125 m 720.25 694.5 b 721.875 694.125 724.875 693.125 728.125 692 731.625 703.625 725.125 716.125 733.875 728.875 728.625 727.25 724.875 725.875 721.125 725.125 720 724.875 718.5 726 717.125 726.5 706.5 731.25 699.75 726.75 699.125 715.125 698.875 708.5 701.375 701.5 696 695.25 699.625 694.125 702.875 693.125 707.25 691.875 707.25 700 707.125 707.375 707.25 714.75 707.375 719 707.25 724.25 713.25 724.25 719 724.125 721.875 720.25 721.375 714.125 720.875 708 720.75 701.875 720.25 694.5 m 1141.875 691.625 b 1152.625 691.625 1158.875 698.25 1159 709.75 1159.125 721.875 1152.875 728.5 1141.5 728.375 1130.5 728.125 1124.875 721.875 1124.875 709.875 1124.875 698.125 1131 691.625 1141.875 691.625 m 1150.875 710.625 b 1150.375 707.25 1150.875 704.125 1149.5 702 1147.625 699.125 1144.375 695 1141.75 695.125 1139.125 695.125 1134.875 699.25 1134.25 702.25 1133.25 707.875 1133.625 714 1134.75 719.75 1135.25 722 1139.125 725 1141.5 725 1144 725.125 1147.375 722.5 1148.75 720.125 1150.375 717.25 1150.25 713.5 1150.875 710.625 m 862.75 709.875 b 862.75 722 857.25 728.125 846.125 728.375 834.75 728.5 828.75 722 828.75 709.75 828.875 698.125 835 691.625 845.875 691.625 856.75 691.625 862.75 698.125 862.75 709.875 m 854.625 708.375 b 854.375 707 854.625 703.375 853.125 700.875 851.625 698.25 848.375 695 845.875 695 843.375 694.875 840 698 838.625 700.625 837.125 703.25 837.125 706.875 837.125 710 836.875 720.125 840.25 725.625 846 725.5 851.5 725.25 854.375 720 854.625 708.375 m 887.625 694.875 b 885.5 695.25 883.5 695.625 880.375 696.25 882.25 706.375 876.25 717.375 884.5 727.125 879.625 727.125 874.25 727.125 867.75 727.125 874.375 722.625 872.75 716.25 872.375 710.625 872.125 704.875 875.375 698.25 870.125 694.875 871.125 691.125 872.25 688.125 872.75 685 874.125 675.5 883.75 670.375 891.375 675.5 893.125 676.625 894.125 678.875 894.875 680.75 895.125 681.375 893.625 682.625 893 683.625 891.375 682.25 889.875 681 888.25 679.75 887 678.75 885.5 676.75 884.5 677 883.25 677.25 881.625 679.125 881.25 680.5 880.5 684.125 880.5 687.875 880.25 691.875 883 692.5 885.375 692.875 887.625 693.375 887.625 693.875 887.625 694.375 887.625 694.875 m 1008.875 709.5 b 1001.625 709.5 994.5 709.5 984.5 709.5 987.75 715.5 989 722.125 992.375 723.375 996.625 725 1002.5 722.25 1006.875 721.5 1006 726 1000.5 729.125 992.25 728.125 982.5 726.875 977.375 719.5 978.125 707.875 978.75 698 985.125 691.5 994.25 691.625 1003.125 691.75 1008 697.375 1008.875 709.5 m 1000.5 706.375 b 1000.625 700.875 1000.875 695 994.25 694.875 987.5 694.75 986.875 700.5 987 706.375 991.625 706.375 996 706.375 1000.5 706.375 m 1274.5 721.5 b 1271.875 727.375 1264 730.25 1255.625 727.25 1247.875 724.375 1243.875 714.875 1246.25 704.5 1248.125 695.75 1255 690.625 1263.5 691.75 1271.75 692.75 1276.125 698.75 1276 709.625 1268.875 709.625 1261.75 709.625 1251.875 709.625 1255 715.5 1256.375 722 1259.875 723.375 1264 725 1269.875 722.25 1274.5 721.5 m 1268.875 706.375 b 1267.375 700.875 1268.375 694.375 1261.125 694.75 1254.875 695.125 1254.375 700.875 1254.25 706.375 1258.875 706.375 1263.25 706.375 1268.875 706.375 m 665.75 709.5 b 658.625 709.5 651.375 709.5 641.75 709.5 644.5 715.125 645.5 720.375 648.75 723.125 654.625 728.25 659.75 722.875 665.25 718.625 661.875 727.125 654.75 730 646.125 727.5 637.75 725 633.625 715.875 635.75 704.625 637.5 695.875 644.375 690.75 653 691.75 661.25 692.625 665.625 698.625 665.75 709.5 m 658.375 706.375 b 657.25 700.75 657.625 694.25 650.625 694.75 644.375 695.25 644 700.875 643.875 706.375 648.625 706.375 653.125 706.375 658.375 706.375 m 1279.625 716.875 b 1285.375 720.875 1288.25 724.125 1291.875 725.125 1294 725.625 1297.875 723.25 1299.5 721 1300.125 720 1297.875 715.875 1296 714.125 1293 711.625 1289 710.25 1285.875 707.75 1279.75 702.75 1281.125 695.5 1288.625 692.75 1298.5 689 1305.125 692.125 1305.5 700.5 1302.625 698.5 1299.875 695.75 1296.625 694.875 1294.875 694.25 1292.25 696.875 1290 698 1291.25 700 1292 702.5 1293.75 703.75 1297 706.375 1301.25 707.75 1304.5 710.375 1310.625 715.5 1309.5 724.125 1301.875 726.375 1296.75 728 1290.625 727.875 1285.25 726.75 1283.125 726.375 1282 721.25 1279.625 716.875 m 754 727.125 b 748.75 727.125 743.625 727.125 738.25 727.125 743.25 720 743.125 701.25 737.625 695.25 742.25 695.625 745.875 688.75 750.375 695.25 750.5 695.375 752.625 693.375 753.875 693.25 756.875 693 760 692.875 762.75 693.625 763.625 693.875 763.625 697.375 764 699.375 762.25 699 760 699.125 758.875 698 753.75 692.625 750.875 698.125 750.375 701 749.375 708 749.875 715.375 750.125 722.5 750.25 723.875 752.375 725.25 754 727.125 m 1093.5 694.75 b 1098.375 696.125 1102.25 689.25 1106.875 695.625 1108.25 694.625 1110 693 1111.875 692.5 1113.875 692 1116.5 692 1118.125 692.875 1119.625 693.625 1120.375 695.875 1120.875 697.75 1121 698.375 1119.125 700.375 1119 700.25 1116.875 699 1114.75 697.5 1112.625 696 1104.25 700.125 1102.625 719.625 1110.75 727.125 1105 727.125 1099.625 727.125 1094.25 727.125 1099.75 720.875 1099.75 700.875 1093.5 694.75 m 933.5 724.875 b 921.25 731.625 915 728.125 914.875 716.125 914.875 710.875 915.125 705.625 914.75 700.5 914.625 698.25 913 696.25 912 694 914.75 690.875 918 687 922 682.25 922.375 685.625 922.625 688.625 923 692 925.625 692.5 928.375 693 931.125 693.375 931.125 693.875 931.125 694.25 931.125 694.75 928.5 695.25 925.875 695.75 922.625 696.375 922.625 704 922.625 711.75 922.625 719.375 922.625 723.5 924.75 725.25 928.875 724.5 930 724.375 931.25 724.625 933.5 724.875 m 1314.125 694 b 1316.875 690.625 1320.125 686.75 1324 682.125 1324.25 685.625 1324.5 688.625 1324.875 692 1327.5 692.5 1330.125 693 1332.875 693.375 1332.875 693.875 1332.875 694.375 1332.875 694.75 1330.375 695.25 1327.875 695.625 1324.5 696.25 1324.5 703.875 1323.875 711.875 1324.875 719.625 1325.25 722.125 1329.75 724 1333.125 726.75 1330.25 726.875 1325.75 728.375 1322.125 727.25 1319.75 726.5 1317.375 722.25 1317 719.375 1316.25 713.25 1317 706.875 1316.625 700.625 1316.5 698.5 1315 696.375 1314.125 694 m 1090.25 727.375 b 1085.875 727.375 1081 728.625 1077.5 726.875 1074.875 725.625 1073.375 720.5 1073 717 1072.25 711.625 1073 706 1072.625 700.5 1072.5 698.375 1071 696.375 1070 694 1072.75 691 1076.125 687.125 1080 682.625 1080.375 685.75 1080.875 688.75 1081.375 692.125 1083.875 692.625 1086.25 693 1088.75 693.5 1088.75 693.875 1088.75 694.25 1088.875 694.625 1086.375 695.125 1083.875 695.75 1080.75 696.375 1080.75 704.125 1080.75 711.875 1080.875 719.5 1080.875 726.5 1086 724.5 1090.25 724 1090.25 725.125 1090.25 726.25 1090.25 727.375 m 692.75 727 b 688.25 727.125 683.375 728.625 679.75 727 677.25 725.875 675.625 720.75 675.125 717.25 674.375 712.125 675.125 706.75 674.75 701.5 674.625 698.875 673.125 696.375 672.25 693.875 674.875 690.875 678.125 687 682 682.5 682.375 685.625 682.625 688.625 683 692 685.625 692.5 688.375 693 691.125 693.5 691.125 693.875 691.125 694.375 691.125 694.75 688.625 695.25 686.25 695.625 682.75 696.25 682.75 704.125 682.25 712.375 683.125 720.375 683.375 722.375 688.25 724 692.75 727
Strengthening security on the school grounds?
That's right. There are rumors of a pervert lurking about.
Meanwhile, the kingdom is faced with the enormous problem that is the Ragnarok.
The Ragnarok...
I intend to fight it for the
sake of this new kingdom.
Defeating that man didn't make much difference, so don't blame yourself.
I know another Drag-Knight who can stand against the Ragnarok.
Who?
Celistia Ralgris.
A daughter of one of the Four Great Houses, and the strongest third-year student here.
Yes. She'll be back from the capital soon.
But if what I heard is correct...
Yeah, she can't stand men.
And I have to speak to her.
Well, I'm sure you'll make due.
But...
Back to more pressing affairs, are you going to help us patrol the school grounds?
Yes, of course. I'd be glad to help.
Thank you.
Then let's get down to business!
Yes!
Quickly, Shalice, do it!
Accept your fate.
The less you resist, the sooner it'll be over.
What?! Are you going to—
Wait!
Stop!
I understand someone had to be bait,
but I never expected this to happen to me.
I wonder what kind of person she is,
this so-called "strongest third-year student".
I'm telling you, I was the one who volunteered to stay in the capital by myself.
I don't mean to brag,
but I think it was the right call.
Who could that be?
Still, I didn't really expect everyone to go back without me.
No, I'm not at all bitter about it, of course.
She's talking to a cat?!
Please wait! I wasn't done talking yet!
And the cat ran away from her.
Wait! Please come back!
Who is she?
Huh?
Shit! This must be the suspicious guy!
I can't allow this.
My judgment is to not allow it.
I will allow you to drop your weapon and surrender.
You have no right to refuse.
Look out!
Are you all right?
I-I'm fine.
What about you?
I'm okay.
Let's go to the infirmary.
Take off your jacket.
We must treat the wound hastily.
U-Um... You see...
Uh, oh. I'm still dressed as a girl!
Hurry up. You don't want that to leave a scar, do you?
Um... Could you do it from behind me?
There. You should be fine now.
Does it hurt?
I'm fine. Thank you.
You're pretty muscular.
Do you practice with a sword often?
Um... Well...
Sorry. That was a rude thing to say to a girl.
I don't mind.
By the way, weren't you
talking to a cat back there?
D-Did you see that?!
Please forget it!
You must have been mistaken.
I didn't mean it like that.
It's not as though I have no one to talk to,
or have no friends! No, nothing of the sort!
A-All right.
Wh-What's important is that your injury was not severe.
But please don't be reckless.
It's my duty to protect the younger girls.
I'm glad you weren't hurt either.
You certainly are a handful, aren't you?
By the way, I haven't seen you here before.
Um... My name is L-Luno.
I'm Celistia Ralgris. You can call me Celis.
Let's meet again some time.
I've taken somewhat of a liking to you.
Celistia...
So she's the strongest student in
the school, and she can't stand men.
Lux.
Lux!
Oh, sorry.
It's only noon. Are you tired already?
No, it's just that I was patrolling the grounds last night.
Oh, that's too bad.
I wanted to help you with your studies again today.
Krulcifer!
Or maybe you'd prefer to take a break
and go out into the city with me?
N-No, I'm still—
Hey! Why are you still flirting?!
I thought that "pretend dating" thing was over!
Oh, was it?
Don't play dumb! Get your hands off of him!
What about you? Can't you tell you're squeezing Lux too hard?
Can't you tell that you're bothering Lux?!
Um... Everyone's staring at us, you know.
My, my. Is the princess afraid to face reality?
What?!
It's you!
You came to get me out of here, right?
My sword friend!
Trust me. I won't let that brat beat me again.
I'll use all the assets at my disposal to buy new armaments through you.
And then—
Huh? What are you doing?
Why?!
Why do you forsake me?!
You put that Ragnarok seed in me!
I've made up my mind.
I have to try talking to Celis about the Ragnarok as well.
Luxy, there's trouble!
I'm telling you, there's no reason Lux can't attend this school!
We can't expel him now!
Tillfur!
I brought him!
All right. Everyone, clear a path!
It was decided during my absence.
Making an exception undermines everything this school stands for.
How stubborn can you get?!
Excuse me!
Lux.
So you are Lux Arcadia.
This is the first we've met.
My name is Celistia Ralgris.
Y-Yes. Nice to meet you.
I'm grateful to you for saving the school
in a moment of need during my absence.
However, as you are a man,
this is no place for you.
Wait! Without Lux here how are we going to face the Abysses and the rebel army?
Not an issue.
I can handle a dangerous mission like that alone.
There is no need to seek the assistance of a man.
Please wait!
I'd like to ask a favor of you
concerning that matter.
Allow me to participate in the subjugation of the
Ragnarok that Lord Balzeride was to carry out.
Lux?
This a threat to the new kingdom.
It is of no concern to you.
If the Ragnarok revives, I'll fight it alone.
In that case, I cannot leave this school yet.
I'm aware of how strong you are,
but the Ragnarok is a formidable enemy.
I cannot allow you to face that danger by yourself!
Were you not listening?
I do not intend to allow your—
Settle down a bit, you two.
In summary, Lux wants to remain in the school and assist in the fight against the Ragnarok.
That's right.
And Celis wants Lux to
leave the school, correct?
But the opinions of the students
are also divided.
So how about you two fight it out?
Huh?
What are you saying?
In three days, there will be a training camp
of the knight squadron at Ries Island.
I want you to decide whether to accept him
after seeing Lux's skills and fighting him there.
Or are you getting cold feet, earl's daughter?
I am of course betting on Lux winning.
Very well.
Until we meet at Ries Island then.
Excuse me.
Do not think you can defeat me.
Celis!
Let's go, Saniya.
Celis.
Thank you for what you did today.
You negotiated his expulsion in order to restore the spirit of the school.
Don't worry yourself, Saniya.
I share a desire with you to
distance him from the fighting.
As you say. Good night, Celis.
This is fate.
For him and me to have to fight like this.
However, there is but one path before me.
This is the only way I can protect both him and the school.
I'm doing the right thing, aren't I, Mr. Wade?
Everyone's off the ship, right?
Yes, ma'am!
Then let's begin training immediately.
What? Training already?
We should take it easy for the first day.
We have a lighter program today.
We did come for training, after all.
Don't fall behind, Lux.
That girl's "light program" is no joke.
G-Got it.
That building there must be—
Hey, Lux, quit daydreaming or you'll get left behind.
Oh. Right!
We'll start with a hundred swings.
Yes, ma'am!
Too soft!
Step in harder!
Yes, ma'am!
Again!
Man, I thought I'd drop dead right there.
Yeah, but Celis sure is hardcore.
She did twice as much of each exercise.
Yes. That's just like her.
She puts in double anyone else's effort like it's nothing.
She's very diligent and strong.
But it always looks like
something is eating at her.
I see.
All right, then!
Let's go back to our rooms and get some rest.
Ah! Please wait a moment!
I didn't get a chance to return the clothes you lent me.
You're a real man of integrity,
going as far as bringing them to the island.
All right! I'll give them to you as a present.
No, thank you!
Jeez, you're no fun.
Yes. I thought you looked very good in them.
I never want to put them on again!
You there, come with me. It's urgent.
What? Me?
Um, I was asked to give you a massage.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Naked?! Celis?!
Is something wrong?
N-No, nothing at all.
Wh-Why is it her?
She can't stand men.
There's no way she asked for me.
Sorry to rush you, but could you start?
Yes, of course.
Thank you.
I'd like to change. Could you turn on the lights?
Um, I'll be leaving then.
At least allow me to thank you first.
P-Please wait!
I need to prepare myself.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Um... well...
Luno! It was you?
It's nice to see you again.
How's your wound?
I didn't know you were here at the camp.
Why don't you stay a bit so we can chat?
U-Um, sorry but I—Uh, I have something else I have to do.
I see. That's a shame.
Then would you join me
during the break tomorrow?
What? But I...
I-I understand if you don't want to.
Th-That's not it. Um, a-all right, I'll be there.
Thank you, Luno!
I'll wait for you in front of the
boarding house after lunch tomorrow.
O-Okay.
I'll take my leave then.
Ah, wait a moment.
Huh?
Did someone misplace this?
No! Th-That's...
Is it yours?
It's a beautiful sword device.
Here. Take good care of it.
I will. Thank you.
Good night.
What are you doing here?
I've never seen you before.
Would you mind telling me
exactly who you are?
Um...
There's no point trying to run.
Wait a moment.
Can you stop interrogating her?
I need her for something.
Krulcifer.
It's rude of you to interrupt me.
Are you not being rude yourself?
You've been lurking in front of that room for a while now.
Would you mind telling me what you were doing?
Excuse me.
Let's go, Lux.
Thank you, Krulcifer.
So you recognized me.
Of course.
How could I not recognize my dearest Lux?
By the way, be very careful.
That girl just now, Saniya Lemiste, is pushing Celis to have you expelled from the school.
Good morning, Lu!
P-Phi!
Wait! This isn't the girls' dorm.
It's a boarding house!
Are you half asleep?!
Lu, want a hug?
If I do this, it'll cheer you up.
Like when my mom did it for me.
You don't have to. I'm not a kid any more.
Have you changed, Lu?
What?
You don't seem any different to me.
I think you're the same kind Lu
you were back then.
Phi!
It's okay.
We haven't changed.
If you lose, I'll fight Celis.
I won't let them expel you.
Thanks, Phi. I'll give it my all.
Good morning.
I'm looking forward to our time together, Luno.
A-As am I.
Let's go!
Okay.
Oh, I've heard that such clothes are in fashion now. Do you like them?
I don't really follow fashion.
I-I see.
Oh, then what about that shop?
Th-This can't go well!
It's supposed to be a dress for sea bathing.
Do you want to try one on too?
Um... I...
I think I have a bit of a cold.
I'm sorry I didn't mean to force you.
It's all right.
I'm sorry. It appears I don't know
how to properly treat younger students.
What?
I've failed at being a good upperclassman.
Father will surely scold me for it. He'll hate me.
Even though I'm the commander of the knight squadron, I...
No, it's not like that.
Really?
Yes. I really enjoyed walking around with you.
You're a kind girl, Luno.
I deeply appreciate hearing that.
These are very good, Celis.
I...
Don't worry about it.
This is our time to relax.
No! I'm the commander of the knight squadron.
I can't show any weakness!
Do you pretend to be perfect all the time?
Listen up, Luno.
A strong person is a person who can bear loneliness.
So you don't need to worry about me.
Luno?
I'm sorry. I just remembered you talking to that cat.
Y-You still remember that?!
Please forget about it!
It's not as though I harbored loneliness while alone in
the capital for so long, which then suddenly exploded!
You keep digging yourself into a deeper hole.
It's so depressing.
And for some reason people
think that I can't stand men.
Hold on a moment! What did you just say?
Luno, can you keep a secret?
Yes.
I, um...
I actually don't have anything against men.
What?!
kusaki mo nemuru yoru no sumi de sekai no fushi de
In the nook of night where even trees sleep, in a cranny of the world
neiki ni sotto mimi wo tatete hitomi wo tojiru
I hear the breath of someone asleep nearby,
close my eyes, and prick up my ears
kubisuji ni futto atatakana inochi no tsubu ga
A warm seed of life near my neck
koko ni iru tte sakenderun da koe naki koe de
is screaming that it's there, in a voice without voice
umarekawaretara owarinaki you ni
If we can be reborn endlessly
kimi ga nodo wo itamenakute
Let's take such forms
sumu you na sugata ni narou
that we won't need to scream so hard to be heard
sashiatatte futari tabi doko made arukeru
Now we're traveling, the two of us. How far can we go?
ikeru toko made ikou hohaba awasete
Let's go as far as we can, matching each other's pace
tsukiatatte futari tabi koko made kureba
And when we finally get to the end of the path, the two of us
kigi ni natte tachitsukusou
Let's become trees and stay there
raise ni natte mo zutto koko de nemurou
Even in the next world, let's keep sleeping there
futari nemurou towa ni
The two of us, let's sleep for eternity